hello everyone it is your host Seth the
programmer and with me today I have my
good ol pal collide and today we're
gonna be talking about Ichigo versus the
Akatsuki now we're doing this video
because we need more bleach content on
the channel we have our magnum opus
coming in you know we're making Ichigo
vs. Naruto fully animated and all that
and it's a little bit weird that I've
been binge reading and watching and all
of this stuff for Bleach and I haven't
made a single bleach related video
really since moderate vs. Aizen so I
decided to get the bleach guy you know
Clyde on here and how are you doing
today climb I'm doing fantastic Jeff
thank you for having me on the channel
once again so sad that I have spent the
past good two or three days weary
watched a heap of the fights from Bleach
and also ran through them too so we can
see if we could find any sort of things
here and there South also found
something very interesting which I'll
talk about later on through the video
and that is a few data book related
things which bleach actually lacks if
you're a bleach fan you'll know that
it's quite hard to find a lot of our
feet and speed and DC related stuff for
Bleach because they just don't usually
give it to us but Seth did find some
very interesting data book related stuff
and thanks to his friend who speaks
fluent Japanese we were able to get a
translated so that's something to look
forward to with this video but I'm super
happy to be on because we do have naruto
vs ichigo coming later on through the
year we're being hyping it up for almost
two whole years and yeah a little bit
longer than we thought but it will be
worth it guys so I hope this video as a
substitute for the time being because we
haven't done any bleach content so once
again thanks for having me on so as I
hinted at the beginning of the video
Clyde will be doing pretty much most of
the belief stuff and I will be doing
just about all of the Naruto stuff and
after we kind of could join our opinions
at the end then you'll hear the response
but for now we're gonna kind of go over
each of meta one-by-one we're only gonna
be going over a power and speed very
particularly right now but once we do
our outro after the stats are down we'll
talk more about hacks teamwork and
what's going to happen with the
characters so without further ado Clyde
take it away
to start off the scaling for each euro
I'd like to dedicate the beginning of
this segment by quickly debunking two
things and the scaling of bleach that
have become quite outdated and doesn't
need to be used anymore when it comes to
having bleaching verses matchups it's
just really silly at this stage the
first of those being gains bankai in the
anime and manga of bleach gained spends
the entire fight of each go trolling him
while talking in code there's actually
an interesting moment where each guy
thinks he knows what gains bunk I can do
but gain distinctly saves to himself in
the monologue on the manga and in the
anime that he is impressed by a ichigo's
ability to come up with this hypothesis
from the few encounters with the bankai
though it is in fact incorrect many
people use this to downplay bleach
characters in speed 13 later tells eyes
and his sword isn't as fast as he said
nor is that even the swords main ability
surprisingly people completely forget
this game scene which blows my mind
because it happens during a very
important moment in the story it's
almost impossible to miss not only just
gain explicitly say that that's not how
his sword works but we've seen better
speed feats back in the soul society arc
where each go can cut a majority of B
Aki is 100 million blades and blocks a
weapon that has the power of 3 million
zanpakuto when it is in the process of
executing an individual and let's be
real for a second Ichigo is a 15 year
old boy who only got his palace a few
months ago he went from being relative
to humans in speed to relative to
literal death gods in speed the same way
gains clapping analogy and presses the
average fan of bleach is the same way
that it impressed Ichigo
the other thing I'd like to debunk
really quick is this scan here which is
from the Bleach official character book
code of souls like lightning each very
precious be Akio with godlike speed and
attacks him at close range the problem
with using this statement is that this
is the equivalent to some mythological
wording from folklore that we even
actually use in our real world
throughout history where you'll see
plenty of stories use phrases like
godlike lightning or heavenly power
things along those nature right you know
it's just there to sound impressive now
the reason why using that data books can
and especially the wording and taking it
very hyper literal the reason why it's
silly is because later on Bo
keya blocks the attacks as shown in the
data book itself right ambi akhiya then
doubles his own speed later on and still
can't catch each eager the reason they
attach words like godlike or lightning
or so on and so forth like I just talked
about before with actual IRL folklore is
because it's meant to be impressive and
this is the first showing of ichigo's
bankai on top of this the lieutenants
and captains themselves actually show
better feats and for Ichigo to be only
seen as lightning speed when byakuya
actually complements the speed of his
bankai would be just a tad ridiculous
surprisingly enough though light speed
is actually the most consistent thing in
the story of bleach as even shuhei
hisagi is shown being able to dodge the
nagashi on a beam of light used to
actually save hollows meaning it spits
it out of the sky as fast as possible to
transport them back to hueco mundo if
they're in danger and is constantly
referred to as light by even the head
captain who dismissively tells them not
to bother trying to stop eyes and now
after it covers gain Tosun and himself
no no Issei is also able to tag x-axis
as light and refers to the attacks as
light multiple times throughout the
actual fears translations yet she has no
son poked her of her own and is probably
weaker than the likes of Zeno soos gate
Kermit Donny before she gets her royal
family weapon and she is without a doubt
weaker than the likes of Shi Kai each
year from the soul society our crew has
the power of around 3 million fodder
saarebas as said before alongside the
fact that Orihime can even react to you
heart attacks and block them she was
also shown in the hueco mundo art being
able to tag someone who euros attacks
when he was trying to hurt Ichigo and
what's interesting about some of the
things that she blocks is that these are
attacks that are actually too fast for
Ichigo to move out of the way this is
the same Ichigo who could blitz Quincy
girls who were leagues above little
turtle um pod and she was shown being
able to use hidden kalkaluru to flash
over push another quincy out of the way
and dodged the australian light the
australian light is actually so fast
that pretty much every single Quincy
that it was aimed at was actually hit by
the light itself even Busbee couldn't
dodge delight and he was comparable to
Shi Kai Yamamoto bankai Renji and even
made Toshiro run away he also blitzed
the same Quincy girls Ichigo was
fighting by a one shotting every
single one of them and these are the
same girls that were giving kampachi
trouble after his fight with Gremmie
to put it simple any sorry far around
the rank of code lieutenant level is
most likely FTL quite casually and this
is pretty crazy considering the null
chad and orihime are able to perceive
movements from characters who are far
above them and massively faster than
light
now as for Ichigo speed however said
that I will talk about that at the end
of the video alongside many other FTL
feats that you guys have definitely
never heard of to go over the akatsuki
speed the speed of Naruto is
ever-evolving and honestly can have its
own 30-minute video and still be missing
some parts to it and since we have a lot
of things to go over I'm gonna keep this
as brief as possible since we're
probably gonna go into more detail after
we talk about the stats there are three
metas to naruto speed one is that
lightning timing is considered top-tier
in the verse for joaneen Kakashi is a
legend for cutting a lightning bolt here
and is considered insanely fast by black
zetsu who literally made the shinobi
world and the fourth red COG a stated to
have lightning-fast attacks in the data
book - is the relativistic to light meta
which is even if the fourth right cog a
was low-balled to lightning speed Minato
KCM Naruto and other characters are able
to blitz him by dozens of times
he's usually reach a few percentages of
the speed of light due to such and this
is usually accompanied by a ton of
calculations and pixel scaling and so on
the third is the Lightspeed meta in
which you could point to many things in
Naruto most specifically the data books
that reference things as light such as
Mifune is bijou cloak slashes Haku zeiss
mirrors Dara's laser circus which
refracts off of water particles like
light and even the right car gaze larrya
is described like light although it
questionably contradicts the previous
lightening statement you could make
arguments that the light meta
contradicts a few things such as Kakashi
and the war getting blitz by a
supposedly light speed Haku even though
he should be able to keep up with a much
faster than light Naruto using kauke's
however these aren't important for this
video for now we'll just give everyone
to benefit from the doubt and say that
the Akatsuki who scale pretty
prominently to Kakashi stage Naruto and
so forth would reach most of any of
these
metas at least in reaction or combat
speed as sage mode is described by
Naruto himself as being faster than KCM
in reaction speeds with pain and obito
being able to fight them and the last
time Naruto fought when sage mode was
versus the night tails and versus pain
when talking about ichigo's destructive
capacity or attack potency it's honestly
quite straightforward and simple hueco
mundo Ichigo after his battle with
Grimmjow actually fights quite well
against kruky aura this is the same
earth you're her Grimmjow didn't want to
fight to the point where he actually put
him in a different dimension using the
caja nagashi on now to do this in short
every go Sparta is said to be able to
destroy it lost no chairs with a cron
race arrow this is a rule set by Aizen
and directly stated by aruki aura Sasuke
Aizen being the one from a society of
1000 plus year-old super geniuses that
are actually so intelligent that they
can manipulate reality and life itself
these thousand-year-old
entities would be more than capable to
be able to calculate reiatsu in basic
physics when it comes to their own power
Aizen was even able to calculate the
exact percentage of how weak his crew he
so he was compared to what it could be
at its match potential Holly Bell struck
Sione even comment that grim Jia
shouldn't have released his grundrisse
arrow against Ichigo while in his base
form and Ichigo then goes on to fight
rim jaw in his release state where his
power and speed increases 5 to 10 times
as our horror compares them to bankai
and strength and the Espada's themselves
alongside their sword cement anemic soul
reapers and tight a coup bro describes
them as a hollow parallel Buki auras
base is then comparable to an Ichiro
that's even stronger than this scrim gl
as Aizen states that he masters his hala
fication in this fight meaning earth ura
is without a doubt as strong as released
grim gel now Kuro should easily be this
strong meaning he can destroy a lost no
chairs 5 to 10 times over in his base
form and if he uses his own run racer in
base this could mean that he could have
a several times increase in strength
according to the data book which Seth
actually found and translated himself it
should also be noted that Grimmjow in
his release Sayed actually has a tax
that surpassed his own gran racer which
he could use in his release state yet
Ichigo is able to handle these
tax and seems to be still relative to
each euro so this is how it works
euros base is five to ten times on snow
chairs and destructive capacity times
five to ten once again on top of that
with his first release then another five
three ten times on top of that with his
second release and if lost no chairs is
comparable to taxes Thailand and even a
percentage of say Australia which is a
conclusion most reach whether it's the
scaling of ScrewAttack or even back when
Seth and I rushed out motto reverses
isin video within the span of three days
or just you know goofy power scaling
forums here and they're all over the
internet they all come to a similar and
song so if we use Texas and Akira is one
thousand times his base in his second
release he could easily destroy an area
of 695 million square kilometers this is
a very layman way to do it but it works
now faster loading Ichigo absolutely
stomps this second release earth Yura
and thanks to SEFs research we found out
that the vast oh lordy has to be at
least ten times stronger than you are
because Akira can counter one of its
normal sorrows which Center or school
does this is the only reason you are a
even had a chance in the fight because
the data books directly state that
setter or Skoda's increases its attack
by an order of magnitude orders of
magnitude in physics and so forth being
in order of ten therefore it has to be
at least ten times greater than its
normal power this is consistent
considering grand race arrow which is
stated to be several times great off
several being times three and Akira
introduces his London over lumbago and
cetera Skouras as if they are more
impressive in conclusion the Vasto Lorde
a can easily destroy an area ten times
that of the earth Yura calc which would
be six billion nine hundred million
square kilometers this also isn't even
his max strength because the Vasto Lorde
a wasn't even at full power when he
fought her fury didn't use its own drum
race arrow and it was easily able to
crush and negate the lumps in Overland
Park which our hero decides to use after
his Center or schoolers release arrows
and blacks arrows fail
meaning it's obviously a stronger
technique as I said before if we do
include the fact that Ichigo can easily
counter the Lanza door alone Parker
plays him at full power with a non
she-hulk sure as seen in ichigo's mind
when he trains to beat Aizen and he uses
his own run race error he is without a
doubt ten times six billion nine hundred
million square kilometers making him
able to destroy or cover an area of 69
billion five hundred million square
kilometers
this isn't wank either because the whole
verse movie even comments on how his
normal Saros that covered multiple
layers of hell and blew open the doors
of hell would inadvertently have an
impact on the entire planet
the vaster Lord a is casually considered
a planetary threat by even Yamamoto who
he himself can threaten all of these
soul society while suppressed in the war
which is actually a parallel world to
the world of the living for destructive
capacity or attack potency most
calculations for the Akatsuki and their
strongest jutsu tend to hit 10 to the 21
joules which is usually considered
enough to destroy small countries in
terms of raw energy output and many of
those are high bald like dataries z0
including the shockwave of the blast and
most coughs which reaches 20 kilometers
in the data book in which they'll also
add that that shockwave is actually how
much it vaporizes to be generous some
cows even go balls to the wall place
pains to Baku Tensei at over 10 to the
23 joules in place pains ship Baku
Tensei and over 10 to the 23 joules of
raw kinetic energy I've even seen some
trying to place them at Continental
other than this you have to make a lot
of scaling assumptions to really get
them higher like finding ways to scale
the caste of the later war are
characters like the ninetails who stated
to be a threat to the entire planet
numerous times in the data book however
this is really work in a lot of
instances and the ninetails tends to
dominate any Akatsuki member comes
across including the Chewbacca Tensei as
well as the fact that stronger attacks
like the c0 is tinct by Magda's body the
sage snake who is rivaling more so a few
tails at the version to nine-tailed
cloak using Orochimaru rather than the
actual full-blooded knight tales at the
absolute best you might be able to get
them to scale to killer B who in his
eight tails state could sum out fight
against the incomplete 10 tails however
it's hard to say exactly how strong it
was as gnar still had an even bully
mastered his link with Kurama it was
constantly low on stamina for a lot of
that encounter giving the benefit
now you could say that the eight-tails
might be able to rival the multi
continental attacks of the tenth tale
that it could poop out although we've
all seen how in reality the ten tails
can kind of flick away anything the
eight tails can actually do and even
then it's hard to scale the Akatsuki to
killer B anyway as even kisame who
actually fought him one of the stronger
members never actually took on a
full-powered b and was constantly
draining his power from him which would
have made the gap close even further
which would be more so an amped kisame
if anything at best you might be able to
say
Obito might scale to the night tails
since he could control it with his eyes
when he was like 14 and that Minato
thought that Naruto would need the night
tails mastery and even then it might be
questionable if he stands a chance all
right fellas so I hope this HG reverses
the Akatsuki video has lived up to its
expectations we're being hyping it up
for quite a while took a very long time
to our make but it has been worth the
long wait itself Seth do you want to
give them a general rundown of how this
fight would actually go down because
we've covered everything to do with the
Ecosse and Ichigo but how about the
fight actually guard after the pole will
break down to beat a and we briefly went
over everything and look look how long
the videos been and we still have so
much more to go over so even with this
outro we're still not gonna be able to
go over everything so we're probably
gonna be making more Naruto versus
Bleach diverse content in the future to
kind of go over more details but for now
I'll keep it brief stats and speed
comparison speed wise it's pretty it's
pretty contentious it's like you could
argue both of these forces are reaching
a similar 10 to the 21 joules of
destructive output or attack potency at
their strongest or maybe more so higher
for Ichigo especially using those okey
doke Alex that Clyde presented earlier
and it really should be noted that most
of these attacks by the Akatsuki that do
reach these country quote-unquote as the
versus community would like to label
that it usually requires most of their
more powerful attacks like Daedra
literally committing suicide pain giving
himself like a brain hemorrhage while he
tries to like hold down the night tails
with this Chewbacca 10 say the Susanoo
ripping Itachi's body apart things like
that it's not necessarily casual whereas
with Ichigo he's just doing it with
every single attack he throws like a
damn Dragon Ball character in speed like
I said before it depends on what
Mehta you're using and you really really
have to give them both the benefit of
the doubt for them to reach those 10
through 100 times the speed of light
ranges but they do bulk tend to reach
near those areas if you hai bought the
Akatsuki and you really give them the
method now it's actually easier than it
is for Ichigo because each go requires
more assumptions however the power
difference is still there and obviously
attack range and stamina goes in
ichigo's favor Ichigo has enough stamina
to fight for months on end without
stopping rest the Akatsuki their
strongest attacks defy ichigo with their
really not doing a whole lot so it
doesn't really matter even if you did
wank off the akatsuki speed in that area
now as I mentioned earlier the hell
verse stuff is actually very important
for this video because it really slaps
into people's faces that the Vasto Lorde
8 is planet level and Kubo takes things
from the filler the movies and it kind
of works in the same way when it comes
to canonicity as dragon ball does where
toe a and p rot have sort of an
influence over bleach and dragon bolt
they can sort of add things into the
story with the movies crew bo approves
them if you just like some stuff he'll
maybe comment on them here and there
which is i think people are gonna bring
up when it comes to how verse movie but
he is directly credited in the opening
and the actual cover of the movie itself
so we have no reason to distrust that
and considering the fact that he does
use stuff directly from the filler and
the actual movie 1 and puts it into the
manga it's like well it's not only
muster dispute here is there sir you
have yamamoto confirming his planet
level ichigo is anywhere from 10 through
a hundred times the speed of light he's
easily you know as i said planet level
once again not looking too good and
that's pretty much in for the Canon of
the movie itself yeah so Canon is a very
subjective in broad area of debate and
once again could have its own video but
in this case Canon is just more so can
it be used during the discussion there
are obviously like particular
definitions of Canon which this wouldn't
apply to however in this case it does
apply I do believe and as Clyde
described now the reason we bring this
up is obviously Ichigo himself in that
movie actually thought that his hollow
form was enough to destroy the whole
world
and Yamamoto actually credits Ichigo for
cutting something that everyone thought
was uncuttable yamamoto being a being
who's so powerful he can destroy the
planet by standing there believes they
were uncuttable as well so that is also
something to think about now even
you do just say like maybe that's too
big and Ichigo does get offed there's
obviously the war arced Ichigo which his
base form is rivaling his vast Oh Lord a
state pretty casually at least in the
statement of you ha and then he can
multiply all his stats by over 30 times
using a bankai which is ten times him
but obviously his several-fold
multiplier of his grand race arrows and
then obviously his speed would go up by
ten times as well and there's just
really no way for the Akatsuki to reach
those levels if it was more arc and you
would really have to just deny ichigo's
Vasto Lorde a lor now other than that
there are hacks the Akatsuki have like
sasori's poison which I will hand over
to Clyde for that one now I know a lot
of Naruto fans are gonna bring up the
idea that well if they work as a quote
team with all the we've all heard the
meme of you know the teamwork stuff they
could probably poison Ichigo and then he
just gets named from that because
there's nothing he can do well sadly
when Seth and I went through bleach once
again we noticed that up if you have
high enough we're out so you can negate
poisons because Yami does it to a frosty
owner who covers his body with this
poison that can actually a road a
concrete also Ichigo is able to fight
against gain who gains bankai it stated
that his actual poison can erode cells
when he gets clipped by the bankai
itself he explains his two eyes and by
each go does get stabbed by the bankai
and yet he doesn't take any damage from
the poison so it's not looking too good
when it comes to that so I wouldn't have
too much confidence in poison if I were
you guys personally I don't believe that
game's poison touched Ichigo but that is
something to consider that it might have
raised him when it went by but the
fractions poison being so strong it
dissolves concrete is a little bit
different than salary's poison which
probably just attacks like via proteins
in the body I mean if they could tank
that much more potent physical poison I
don't really see any evidence that
acessories work now other than that
there is data receive alms
now in this debate we are obviously
saying okay the Akatsuki can see Ichigo
otherwise they're fighting a an
invisible spirit man that they don't
even know exists now you could say that
chakra is spiritual in nature and
therefore they can sense Ichigo however
if you grant that benefit of the doubt
to the Akatsuki then Ichigo can see
chakra because chakra is spiritual in
nature as well if you're linking one
thing yet the link the other and in this
case Ichigo would be able to see the
bombs and then there's even the argument
whether it effect each go regardless
I mean it didn't even rip apart Mondas
body and Monda is considered weaker than
Orochimaru if he had his arms and as
well as the fact that Monda is in
Orochimaru or more so rivaling Naruto
with a few tales of diversion to nine
tails cloak not anywhere close to the
full thing so it's really once again
hard to argue that they would do
anything now next there's pain and zetsu
now pain and zetsu and obito they do
kind of scale to that late war era if
you use the fact that pain was stealing
away the nine tails there's more
arguments than that but just keeping it
brief he is able to maybe like hold down
the eight tails of the nine tails which
is pretty considerable since it's a
planet Buster in its full state zetsu
who was so powerful that he was able to
amp Obito to fight late war Kakashi
Minato and a lesser zetsu was able to
hold off the whole shinobi alliance so
these two characters once again even if
they do beat master Lord a they're
getting negged once again by war arc
ichigo they do not have the same brow
busting or speed feats to really compete
with that unfortunately next is Itachi's
genjutsu Itachi's genjutsu unfortunately
while it may work on a jinchuriki as
implied by Naruto with his tsukuyomi at
least there's no evidence that it would
work on Ichigo who has two spirits and
both of those spirits are more than
likely more powerful than the Bijou
within a jinchuriki especially a lesser
jinchuriki not even the nine tails
jinchuuriki this would also apply to
Obito who as a koto a matsutake like
genjutsu he placed on yara so the
problem with those theories is that
obviously the genjutsu placed on yagura
or Filas placed on the eight tails would
not be nearly the same as if it was
placed on the nine tails as we've seen
even Madra you see ah in his battle with
hoshi Rama or Obito versus Minato Minato
states if he's anything like Madara he
cannot hold the nine tails for very long
and his genjutsu and it is known
throughout the land the holding the nine
tails and again jutsu is insanely
difficult despite the fact that the
tailed beasts are constantly put under
genjutsu including the eight tails he
was put under again jutsu by Orochimaru
at least in filler and he doesn't even
have a Sharingan and then obviously
there's the toast Keyblade and I'll let
Clyde go for that one now as for the
telescope blade it's um it's a little
bit weird because
people could say that it kind of works
the same way as some pop Tories doing
bleep so it may not even affect Ichigo
for that matter or we could even make
the argument that he's even too quick to
even be hit by the thing and if they if
the Akatsuki themselves are to seal
Ichigo with that with a slash way Itachi
is already you know in pain from using
the Susanoo itself it isn't looking too
good and on top of that it uh it isn't
really a fair thing to say that it could
exactly cut just anybody because that
would be a quote no-limits fallacy
considering that Kakashi's lightning
blade is actually sated that our
Kakashi's arm becomes a famous blade
that can cut through anything through
anything so if we went to wank the Tasca
blade it's it is a bit unfair to give it
that much credit I just don't think it's
gonna be as handy as a lot of people are
gonna say in this battle and on top of
that like even just hitting Hur lines
gonna be too much trouble yeah obviously
the Tosca blade it attacks things you
have to stab them for it to seal not
even just cut however obviously when it
comes to the war aki geo yet the
peruvian fast and then you have to prove
once again that it actually has the
power required to cut someone on that
level you can't just have a no limits
fallacy where you can just cut through
absolutely everything especially
universe like bleach where hacks are
negated by raw power and obviously it
goes back to Kakashi and Kakashi she's a
character who couldn't even he couldn't
even cut through like most of the
version to Jin Turkey he did cut through
a lot of them however there are many
instances where it was more like who's
throwing a hard punch like next to a guy
so it is a little bit weird to use that
comparison that also goes back to Hidan
Ichigo has a zanpakuto which is a Soul
cutter and it actually attacks you on a
spiritual level
so if Ichigo were to annihilate or fully
attack he'd on who does not have the
durability to withstand any of his
attacks he not is not getting up from it
his soul will be annihilated and his
body will be vaporized even if he was
immortal we have seen that he Don's body
isn't like majin buu where we like
recovers or like regenerates itself
instantly yes have conquers you put back
on his head and stuff like that so if
his body is like atomized or he's just
completely removed from existence which
Quincy's are actually able to remove
people from existence let alone Ichigo
who is also his Quincy powers it's not
looking good for hidan same would go for
a kakuzu and Conan they aren't really
doing much either especially since
they're raw power based fighters and
Ichigo has more raw power and months
more stamina than they do
yeah just weak
Modern Warfare 2 claymore said I been
doing she's a filler character in this
one and finally just one more thing to
mention is that a lot of people will say
just like the Tosca blade well what if
Ichigo gets thrown in obito's karma we
dimension well there are some big issues
that Obito has and that's that not only
can hollows especially at the level of
earth your own above which Ichigo
absolutely is in the wake of mondo saga
let alone the the war arc okay he can
literally just break out of a dimension
and he could also open up the nagashi on
which hollows can do they could just
open up a portal and leave if you want
to blank ichigo's Shinigami form I don't
even know if he can do this but he could
technically open up the senkaimon and
leave so he's got like three options
there may be two of you know two at best
but still yeah there's nothing that
Obito can do to him either so not
looking too good once again at the end
of the day Ichigo is more of a rival to
the Akatsuki and as a spark I don't care
if you think the akatsuki beats a spot
our Ichigo if you think a spot our key
Ichigo beats the Akatsuki I just want us
all to universally agree the war arc
what's that which of course we'll be
going into more detail in naruto vs
ichigo and other than that speaking of
naruto if you guys want to see in naruto
versus the Espada maybe you can go over
which arcs of Naruto compared to the
Espada then it hit us up wall gladly do
that as well and in the meantime check
out moderate IRS's the Akatsuki if
you're looking for more inverse scaling
until next time
[Music]